[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 7, "question": "You still take baths together in a huge bathtub with wine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 8, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 9, "question": "Well, what about that - where did you get that from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "IN", "DT", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 10, "answer": "My sources.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "Did you wake up this morning and have a quick, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "I probably did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "What do you see your role as these days?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, I'm a woman who's interested in a lot of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Any response?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Yes, I like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "But what do you think the secret of longevity in a marriage is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Listening is one of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "Where'd you get that from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "My sources.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "How far do you feel America has now come since then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "Well, we've come pretty far.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Are you pleased that President Obama got reelected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Yes, very much so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "I think he's a good man.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Do you sleep well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "How about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Probably not as well as you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "How are you doing this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "The bathtub is one of the ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "What's that, honey?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "My hair back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "It's great to be acting with those great actors, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Oh, she is great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "So you're enjoying the acting still?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "Oh, I love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Are you kidding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "You do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "So this book you've written, \"Grace, God and Glory: My Leap of Faith\" - has an amazing set of pictures, by the way, how has your life been since this extraordinary summer you had in my home city?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "''", ":", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "It's been a whirlwind, but I'm having so much fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["summer"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "What's been the best moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I would say going to the White House and meeting the president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "What were his first words to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "Well, we had talked to him prior any of the Games, when we won team finals.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "Did he say anything to you about -- about that part of this, that you also had achieved this extraordinary milestone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "Yes, I mean he was telling me that he was so proud of me, and, you know, all hard work pays off.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "How much do you have to work out a day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "I would imagine your routine is agonizing, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Some days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "Are you -- are you sure?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "I used to be a top gymnast, actually.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "No, I lied.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "-- what does it take to be a winner, winner, like a big winner?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "It takes a lot, not only the talent, but you have to be consistent and you have to dedicate your heart into the sport, and you have to work very hard and give 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "And you've got some boys in your life, Gabrielle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gabrielle"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "I just want to go to a nightclub, meet a nice boy, give up gymnastics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I don't think that -- I don't -- no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "So gymnastics is your real love, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Did you feel sad when you wrote it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "Yes, I mean just (INAUDIBLE).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Do you talk to him much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Is it non-existent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "It's pretty distant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "What do you -- why is this non-existent, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, first of all, I've been traveling everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Do you think he knows that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I -- I think he knows that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "I love \"The Vampire Diaries.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "As good as winning gold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "How tall are you without those?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I'm five foot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Are you spending all the money as fast as it's coming in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "No, I am like very frugal, so I save my money.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What's your big ambition now, Rio, presumably?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Are you going to go there and kick butt and win more gold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Who's your hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Well, my hero is definitely my mom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dominique Dawes"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "And who's your sporting hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Dominique Dawes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "I really respect what he set for us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Well, I don't think about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "You don't look in the mirror some mornings and think, I'm an icon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Do you ever get anyone have a go at you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "There's the old saying of, of all the people who don't like me, just think of the millions who've never heard of me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "When you finished the book, what did you think of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "Well, actually, it was a really easy book to write.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "What do you -- what do you make of what's happened to you in those 80 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, it's kind of -- you can't think about all of that at once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Are you a happy guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Oh, I'm very happy right now, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Is this the happiest you've ever been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "This -- yes, as happy as I ever hope to be right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Did you ever meet him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "You went drinking together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "We had a drink together, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "ORGAN: (INAUDIBLE) Jack Daniels?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "I didn't check the label.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Daniels"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "But did you wake up this morning and have a quick, you know, a puff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "I probably did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["this morning"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Do you take a lot of it now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I think some people have more tolerance, you know, for smoking pot than others.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Yes, what do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Oh, I think it's progress, and I think it's, you know, a great step forward, and people are finally growing up and looking around the room and checking things out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "(INAUDIBLE) very well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dolly Parton"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 625, "question": "If you were consigned to a desert island and you could only listen to one song endlessly, on a permanent replay, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "CD", "JJ", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "That would be really hard to say, because, you know, this is -- I've just recorded a song with Dolly Parton that I think is the best song that I ever -- she wrote it and...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "-- I told her, I think this is the best song I've heard in a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "NNS", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "-- that could be a strategy that works?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Oh, I know it would work, because it would be better than the one we have, where there's still drugs available to anybody who wants them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "ORGAN: When you look at the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan, what do you think about America's position in the world, its foreign policy in particular in the last 12 years or so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Well, as you probably know and have read, I'm completely against war.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 12 years"], "LOCATION": ["Iraq", "Afghanistan", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bible"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "WDT", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Do you see any chance of actual peace in the Middle East?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "Well, if you believe in the Bible, which, of course, it says two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Were you -- were you pleased he got reelected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Yes, I'm glad he got reelected.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "You never voted for anybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "Oh, I have voted, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Did you -- did you this time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Well, I had all kinds of excuses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "JJR", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "You didn't feel passionately enough about either candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "I really felt like Obama was going to win, that he did -- he didn't really need one more vote, that he had already had it sewn up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "CD", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "What do you make of the gun debate in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "Well, you know, I've hunted all my life and (INAUDIBLE) when I was young, I had a bee-bee gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 720, "question": "Are you proud of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 721, "answer": "Oh, very much, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "Do you think you've become a better husband?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "What have you learned about marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "And yet, although you say that, you also always stayed fond of your exes, am I right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 759, "question": "So if I were to ask you how many, of all the girls you've loved before, we would reach, how many would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "Well, you said properly and...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "Well, how would you define properly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "ELSON: Well, that was not what I said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "How many times have you been in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Is she the -- is she the real love of your life, would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "Well, for the moment, she is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 801, "question": "ELSON: Do I ever sing songs to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 802, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "You -- are you a romantic at heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "Oh, 100 percent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "If I could let you relive a moment, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "I don't know, that's a -- that's a difficult one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "What's the great light (ph) for you, personally, for whatever reason?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Every time I go do a show where I show up and they show up and they come and clap and pay good money to hear, you know, hear me sing songs, it doesn't get any better than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 861, "question": "How do the people that supply the original content feel about you nicking their stuff?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 862, "answer": "Well, we are not substituting it, we still allow you to read the full story.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", ":", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 871, "question": "But where is the money?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 872, "answer": "So we're kind of just taking it out (ph) by the user response.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 878, "question": "You think you guys just don't get it anymore, you should be doing XYZ?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 879, "answer": "I think the problem is with kind of the digital space is yes, the kind of publishers that have been around with print form for 50, 60, 70, 100 years, and now, I mean in the last five or six years, it's the mobile device has come into play.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["XYZ"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 888, "question": "What's your next great idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 889, "answer": "I was thinking about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "You are going to be (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "Yeah, very soon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 900, "question": "How are you going to deal with becoming stinking rich if that is what happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 901, "answer": "Well, that will be a great day, but I don't think -- look, to be honest, the thing at the moment I'm really focused on is just these users, you know, we have hundreds of thousands users rating it 5 stars in the app store.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 905, "question": "What about school, Nicholas?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 906, "answer": "Yeah, I know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nicholas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 909, "question": "Are you at school?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 910, "answer": "I'm on a sabbatical leave at the moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 914, "question": "Realistically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 915, "answer": "Realistically I think I can find a way of doing both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "You want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "Yeah, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 920, "question": "Given that you created this world-beating app?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 921, "answer": "There is a lot of stuff beyond technology I want to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 923, "question": "Who are you heroes in the tech game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 924, "answer": "You know, Steve Jobs was actually the reason why I taught myself to program.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Yoko Ono"], "LOCATION": ["Dakota"]}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 928, "question": "What has been the single biggest pinch-me moment you've had so far?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 929, "answer": "Probably when I visited Yoko Ono in the Dakota building.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 930, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 931, "answer": "'ALOISIO: Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121222pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 934, "question": "She play \"Imagine\" for you while you were there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 935, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]